

Profile

I am passionate about learning new skills, trying different experiences and discovering the most varied technologies. I am thrilled and enchanted by the universe of programming and the infinite possibilities that are possible from it.

I'm currently working with React Native, along with Typescript, Expo, Redux, Context, Zustand, Firebase, Sentry, Jest, Github Actions, EAS, Styled Components, Restyle, Off-line Database (SQLite) and others.

A little bit more about me:

- 4+ years of experience in mobile development.
- Solid knowledge of React Native, his complete cycle of delivery and its ecosystem.
- 4+ years of experience in remote work.
- Self-taught with great ease in learning new technologies.
- Experience in large-scale applications.

Employment History

Senior Mobile Developer, Mindz, São Paulo

OCTOBER 2023 - PRESENT

As a Senior, I had the mission to build an app to watch class, download and watch offline, do quiz and survey. All the structure of app was made by me and I chose the best tools to make this app in 4 months with the functionality to watch videos offline. Last but certainly not least, I made a process to create whitelabels based in this app.

Mid-level Mobile Developer, MaisTODOS, Ribeirão Preto

SEPTEMBER 2021 — PRESENT

Restructuring of the Cartão de Todos application with more than 4 million registered users.

Rewriting V2 of the application from Javascript to Typescript and from React Native CLI to Expo Managed and with this change it was necessary to change the CI/CD flow, having an integration of Expo with GitHub Actions to comment on Pull Requests and QAs squad to test, generate builds and submit releases. In V3, configurations and writing of tests (unit and End2End), animations with React Reanimated, addition of accessibility to the project and structuring of Deeplink were carried out. And in V4 configuration and implementation of React Query, updating Expo/React Native, security adjustments, addition of Expo-Dev-Client technology with reformulation of our CI/CD flow, which would help the QA team and implementations with libraries.

Furthermore some fixes and features in backend with Python like creation of fields to response, manipulation of datas, queries in database to return in API response and automation of releases creation.

Mid-level Mobile Developer, Compass UOL, São Paulo

NOVEMBER 2019 - JANUARY 2021

I worked with 2 different clients on projects with millions users across Brazil (Assaí and SemParar).

Details

Feira de Santana

Brasil

5575981450448

yuri.ybgt.yfo@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

brazilian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

06/03/2001

Feira de Santana

Links

Instagram

LinkedIn

Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Work in a Team

Communication Skills

SQL

Git

Python

English Communication

JavaScript

Java

Fast Learner

Database

Postgres

Typescript

React Native

Expo

Redux

Zustand

In Assai, I added new features for a new version with a completely different look, such as: screens, animations, Deeplink implementation, refactoring of legacy codes (class components) for functions, styling with Styled Components, global state management with Redux Toolkit, bug fixes and store releases.

Already in SemParar I created new screens implemented with Design System - using the Styled Components tool - refactoring of legacy codes (class components) for functions, using Redux Saga to manage global states and bug fixes.

Developer Assistant, Inventus Tecnology, Feira de Santana

JUNE 2019 - JULY 2019

I worked at Inventus Tecnology for 1 month. I worked there with the development tool that calls "Maker", developing interfaces and forms for the their app. But nothing very advanced. And I started to learn more about database with Postgres.

Education

High School, Colegio Modelo Luis Eduardo Magalhaes, Feira de Santana

JANUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2018

Bachelor, UNIFACS, Feira de Santana

JANUARY 2019 - DECEMBER 2023

Sentry	
Jest	
YML	
Languages	
English	
Portuguese	